<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<!DOCTYPE events [
<!ELEMENT events (event+)>
<!ELEMENT event (title, date, time, location, description)>
<!ATTLIST event type (missions|guest|luncheon|outing|holiday) #REQUIRED>
!ELEMENT title (#PCDATA)>
!ELEMENT date (#PCDATA)>
!ELEMENT time (#PCDATA)>
!ELEMENT location (#PCDATA)>
!ELEMENT description (#PCDATA)>
]>

<events>
  <event type="guest">
    <title> Pastor Tulebot Visits</title>
    <date> Sunday, October 13 </date>
    <time> Regular Sunday service times</time>
    <location> Victory Baptist Church</location>
    <description> Pastor Tulebot will be visiting our church to present the message on Sunday morning. Please also join us for Sunday School and the Sunday evening service to hear about the work he is doing in his and his family&apos;s mission in the Philippines. </description>
  </event>

  <event type="outing">
    <title> Fall Church Picnic </title>
    <date> Sunday, October 20 </date>
    <time> 12:30 PM </time>
    <location> French Park in Plymouth, MN</location>
    <description> After the Sunday morning service, we will have a potluck picnic at French Park in Plymouth, MN. All are welcome to join and encouraged to sign up to bring a food for all to enjoy. </description>
  </event>

  <event type="missions">
    <title> Missions Conference </title>
    <date> October 24-27 </date>
    <time> Evenings at 6:00 PM and regular Sunday service times </time>
    <location> Victory Baptist Church </location>
    <description> Join us and welcome missionaries from all over the world to hear about their outreach and the lives they are impacting. We will also be having an international food potluck to celebrate in fellowship our supported missionaries. </description>
  </event>

  <event type="luncheon">
    <title> Thanksgiving Potluck </title>
    <date> Sunday, November 20 </date>
    <time> 12:30 PM </time>
    <location> Victory Baptist Church </location>
    <description> Following the Sunday morning service, we will be having our annual Thanksgiving potluck luncheon. Please sign up to bring food and join us downstairs for fellowship. Evening service is canceled for this day. </description>
  </event>

  <event type="holiday">
    <title> Thanksgiving Candlelight Service </title>
    <date> Wednesday, November 27 </date>
    <time> 6:00 PM </time>
    <location> Victory Baptist Church </location>
    <description> Our typical Wednesday night Bible Study will be amplified by have the service lit by candlelight. We will also have a time for anyone to give their testimony and describe what they are thankful for. </description>
  </event>

  <event type="holiday">
    <title> Christmas Dinner </title>
    <date> Friday, December 20 </date>
    <time> 6:30 PM </time>
    <location> Dehn&apos;s Diner in Maple Grove, MN </location>
    <description> Everyone is invited to join together at Dehn&apos;s in Maple Gove, MN to gather for a Christmas dinner. There will also be a white elephant gift exchange, Christmas trivia, and great fellowship as we celebrate the birth of our savior, Jesus Christ. </description>
  </event>

  <event type="outing">
    <title> Christmas Caroling </title>
    <date> Sunday, December 22 </date>
    <time> 6:00 PM </time>
    <location> Meet at Victory Baptist Church </location>
    <description> Join us for our annual Christmas Caroling event! We will go out to and sing Christmas songs and hymns to those members of the church who are unable to get out often and many others. We will meet at the church before heading out. This will take place of the Sunday evening service. </description>
  </event>
</events>
